Hi, now our application use live exchange rates, but we want to improve some user experience.
In that lesson, we will ask for sort of to help us make UI smarter, more beautiful with
better experience, and this improvements will make the app feel more professional, friendly
and reliable, and we will ask AI to make these changes.
So, the first change I'd like to make is a limit number of digits in amount, so I would
like to limit it in app 12 and display some message right here.
So, the next change will be, I want to, for B to choose in two same currencies, because
no sense, to compare them, we will make them disabled.
And next one, I'd like to extend the currencies we support, so we will fetch available
currencies from front footer API, and we'll show them, okay, we have some more even.
Yeah, so it's when the API doesn't work, we display some error message here.
Okay, let's first start with the limit in the amount, so what we will do, user should
not enter extremely large amounts, because it can break logic, it's not real use case,
or even can confuse the layout, so you see it's not believable, or it can be displayed
like this, so if you introduce a safe limit as to how much money, how much, how the big
amount can be, so the message explains this rule right here, this will keep your eye clean
and avoid some unexpected behavior, so let's type a prompt, you can find a prompt in one
of the last sound with all the materials, I will ask limit the amount input to maximum
to our digits, before that's the most, and also show small info message below the input
that explains the limit to the user, I'll still use an engine, oh, let's open the
amount input and see how it will work, we can normally should work in this component, might
be a test, so let's see, let's see how you handle it, I see here you can use the maximum
message, okay, that's interesting approach, I was in a kit building with the maximum length,
using HTML attribute, what might be this approach work best better, oh, let's try to make
it bigger, oh, might be it's not yet finished, now it's finished, okay, oh, let's save
it, and refresh page, yeah, we need to start our application, because I did it commit
before, you can see always up to date code source, I will use NPM run dev, and we'll refresh
my page, and now you'll try to enter digits, yeah, you see it's limited, how much, 1, 2,
3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 12, okay, but I will do like this, if I will be right
to target, yeah, it's most, also not allowed, yeah, okay, it's really smart, and we see this
message, okay, with this change, we find, I don't click keep all, the next one, I will
ask to disable the same parenthesis, like for example, if we, from this list, we shouldn't
be able to choose euro, because it's selected here, and from this list, we shouldn't
be able to select power, used it, because it's already selected, so it doesn't make sense
to user, this will prevent some error and create a pretty better experience, I also prepared
some prompt, let's switch to, and I ask, it's able to select in the same parent in
both drop downs, if user selected from currency, disable the same option in to drop down,
and do the opposite as well, that's was, I was explaining to you, make sure users can only
choose two different currencies at all the time, okay, let's ask the implemented, I think
it will change the currency select, and might be also the application dot test fix, our main
file where we dispose the layout, okay, let's wait a bit till he will apply changes,
so he's changing the select, he added disabled quotes, so when we go disable this code,
okay, that's fine, what else he will update, he will update his application, and disabled
quotes is really easy, he already has his values, okay, let's now update page, and
I will try to choose use them is disabled, it's fine, and from the front we are not able
to choose and the error, so it's great, as we'd like, I will click keep changes, and now
we'll implement the last improvement, we'll ask to support the more currencies, instead
of using a fixed list of our currencies, our option to support much more currencies might
be all available currencies, we'll loss this list dynamically from the front footer API,
I suppose it should have some API to display all available currencies, let's search, yes,
it has an API for all available currencies, yeah, I should get all of them, and then display,
what else do we generate also, do we need to generate a mod just for those currencies,
I guess it should be possible on a currency port, so yeah, I should figure out how to do
it, for us, and I already have a prompt, let's paste it, so I ask dynamically
load all supported currencies from front footer API and display dynamically, dynamically
generate like a mod just for each currency, remove all mock data and replace it, it will
be a real data from API, but we don't have a dead code, never heard code currency flag
or modules generated dynamically, please, and if an emoji cannot be generated, show
it without emoji just a currency code, so let's ask and see the result, all like the structure
of application is really good, it's lit up by components, it's really easy to track the
changes, because normally if you need to handle the limit of the amount, we do it in the
amount component, if we need to do something with currency select, we do it inside of it,
it's really good architecture, okay, let's wait, so yeah, it's changing the currency
select, we would change, we update some values, interesting, yeah, because you don't cannot
predict the currency code, so that's why just drink, because we get them from API, and what
else is updating the application, what you're updating, they show me, I'm interesting, okay,
we see changes, we, in use effect, we face list of verbal currencies, you need a mass in
application file, so we can ask him to move it to details, order, because it's not really
good to have this application, to have this, have this function right here, maybe because
he started really good with splitting components, but he did a mass now in the main file,
hey, he finished an update, he also updates the rates, yes, I have to stream, okay, let's
click, keep all, I'll refresh my page, so we now have more currencies, okay, all of them
have a module, so let's check how we generate the modules, the application test, a lot
of symbols, make more currency, okay, define somehow the region, okay, I'm not going to
dive into it, oh, let's try to convert, you know, rate reason pound to, for example, I don't
know, we have to put it so what, what's the rate, okay, if it like 500, yeah, it's updated,
okay, I see a few more improvements, but we'll make them in the next person, so and see
you, for now, with done, we already support a lot of currencies, it's really great, we support
limited number of currencies because they come from European Central Bank, if you'd like
support more currencies, you of course used another API with API key, okay, see you in the next
So that's not what we will do more improvements.